Guide to the William Wolf collection of Buckminster Fuller papers pertaining to the World Game and Design Science Institute M1684
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- William Wolf manuscript material, 3.5 Linear feet
  - re. BF Goodrich agreement (Box 7, Folder 1043)
  - Inquiry letter from S. Mukerjee to R.B. Fuller re. floating breakwater (Box 7, Folder 1044)
  - Letter from E. Tedeschi to W. Wolf re. BF Goodrich agreement (Box 7, Folder 1045)
  - Letter from W. Wolf to E. Tedeschi re. BF Goodrich agreement (Box 7, Folder 1046)
  - Letter from R.B. Fuller to W. Wolf correcting BF Goodrich agreement (Box 7, Folder 1047)
  - Response to inquiry letter of October 5, 1976 from S. Mukerjee to R.B. Fuller, box 7, folder 1044 (Box 7, Folder 1048)
  - Letter from W. Wolf to E. Tedeschi re. Sperry Vickers (India) & others (Box 7, Folder 1049)
  - Letter from V. Smythe to W. Wolf re. corrections to BF Goodrich Agreement (Box 7, Folder 1050)
  - Letter from S. Mukerjee to W. Wolf re. response to letter of July 17, 1976 from W. Wolf to E. Tedeschi, box 7, folder 1049. (Box 7, Folder 1051)
  - Letter from W. Wolf to E. Tedeschi re. corrections to BF Goodrich agreement (Box 7, Folder 1052)
  - Letter from E. Tedeschi to W. Wolf re. BF Goodrich agreement (Box 7, Folder 1053)
  - Letter from W. Wolf to R.B. Fuller re. BF Goodrich agreement (Box 7, Folder 1054)
  - Proposed agreement revisions (Box 7, Folder 1055)
  - Letter from W. Wolf to R.B. Fuller re. BF Goodrich agreements (Box 7, Folder 1056)
  - Addresses re. folks of interest (Box 7, Folder 1057)
  - Fully Executed BF Goodrich agreement (Box 7, Folder 1058)
  - Arte Y Cement interest in publishing re. breakwater (Box 7, Folder 1059)
  - Proposal re. floating breakwater market study (Box 7, Folder 1060)
  - Letter from R.B. Fuller to W. Wolf re. BF Goodrich agreement (Box 7, Folder 1061)
  - Slides of BF Goodrich floating breakwater (Box 7, Folder 1062)
  - Swedish Industrial Development Corp. letter of interest (Box 7, Folder 1063)
  - Letter from W. Galloway to W. Wolf re. agreement extension request (Box 7, Folder 1064)
  - Notes re. floating breakwater company (Box 7, Folder 1065)
  - Letter granting BF Goodrich extension (Box 7, Folder 1066)
  - BF Goodrich floating breakwater report (Box 7, Folder 1067)
  - re. Firestone interest (Box 7, Folder 1068)
  - Letter from D. Nielsen to W. Wolf re. Firestone patent procedures (Box 7, Folder 1069)
  - Letter from E. Tedeschi to W. Wolf re. British tire breakwater (Box 7, Folder 1070)
  - Last letter from E. Tedeschi to W. Wolf - BF Goodrich not interested (Box 7, Folder 1071)
- William Wolf audio material, 0.5 Linear feet
  - Bermuda YPO University for Presidents (Box 8, Reel 2001)
  - Paradise Island YPO University for Presidents. Tape 1 (Box 8, Reel 2002)
  - Paradise Island YPO University for Presidents. Tape 2 (Box 8, Reel 2003)
  - Views of World Game to Date, University of Pennsylvania: DSI dinner (Box 8, Audiocassette 2004)
  - DSI Director's meeting, University of Pennsylvania City Science Center (Box 8, Audiocassette 2005)
  - Fuller, Brooks, Wolf: World Game [2 sides] (Box 8, Audiocassette 2006)
  - Fuller, Brooks, Wolf: World Game (Box 8, Audiocassette 2007)
  - Fuller, Brooks regarding World Game (Box 8, Audiocassette 2008)
  - Fuller, Brooks regarding World Game (Box 8, Audiocassette 2009)
  - Fuller, Brooks, Gabel regarding W. Wolf paper (Box 8, Audiocassette 2010)
  - Fuller, Brooks, W. Wolf: World Game tape 1 (Box 8, Audiocassette 2011)
  - Fuller, Brooks, W. Wolf: World Game tape 2 (Box 8, Audiocassette 2012)
  - Fuller, Brooks, W. Wolf: World Game tape 3 (Box 8, Audiocassette 2013)
  - World Game at Bear Island: tape 1 (includes written transcript) (Box 8, Audiocassette 2014)
  - World Game at Bear Island: tape 2 (Box 8, Audiocassette 2015)
  - Ben Eli, Wolf regarding World Game in New York City: tape 1 (includes written transcript) (Box 8, Audiocassette 2016)
  - Ben Eli, Wolf regarding World Game in New York City: tape 2 (includes written transcript) (Box 8, Audiocassette 2017)
  - World Game in Cambridge: tape 1 (includes written transcript) (Box 8, Audiocassette 2018)
  - World Game in Cambridge: tape 2 (Box 8, Audiocassette 2019)
  - Ben Eli, Wolf regarding World game in New York City: tape 1 (includes written transcript) (Box 8, Audiocassette 2020)
  - Ben Eli, Wolf regarding World game in New York City: tape 2 (Box 8, Audiocassette 2021)
  - DSI meeting in New York City: tape 1 (Box 8, Audiocassette 2022)
  - DSI meeting in New York City: tape 2 (Box 8, Audiocassette 2023)
  - DSI meeting in New York City: tape 3 (Box 8, Audiocassette 2024)